A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the State Coordinator of the Virginia Department of Emergency Management, 1987-2013
Library of Virginia
- Correspondence and subject files (Acc. 53598), 1995-2013.
  - Emergency Management Accreditation Program (EMAP) Compliance, 2004-2005. (Box 1)
  - Emergency Management Accreditation Program (EMAP) Strategic Plan, 2004-2005. (Box 1)
  - Emergency Management Accreditation Program (EMAP) Resources, 2004-2005. (Box 1)
  - Emergency Management Accreditation Program (EMAP) General information, 2004. (Box 1)
  - Emergency Management Accreditation Program (EMAP) Assessment report, 2004. (Box 1)
  - Executive Order 65 - COVEOP, LCAR, 2004. (Box 1)
  - National Emergency Management Association meeting - Accreditation report, 1998 Sept 9. (Box 1)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2005 Jan. (Box 2)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2005 Feb. (Box 2)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2005 Mar. (Box 2)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2005 Apr. (Box 2)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2005 May. (Box 2)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2005 June. (Box 2)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2005 July. (Box 2)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2005 Aug. (Box 2)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2005 Sept. (Box 2)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2005 Oct. (Box 2)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2005 Nov. (Box 2)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2005 Dec. (Box 2)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2006 Jan. (Box 2)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2006 Feb. (Box 2)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2006 Mar. (Box 2)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2006 Apr. (Box 2)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2006 May. (Box 2)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2006 June. (Box 2)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2006 July. (Box 2)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2006 Aug. (Box 2)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2006 Sept. (Box 2)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2006 Oct. (Box 2)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2006 Nov. (Box 2)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2006 Dec. (Box 2)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2007 Jan. (Box 2)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2007- Feb. (Box 2)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2007 Mar. (Box 2)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2007 Apr. (Box 2)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2007 May. (Box 2)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2007 June. (Box 2)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2007 July. (Box 3)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2007 Aug. (Box 3)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2007 Sept. (Box 3)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2007 Oct. (Box 3)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2007 Nov. (Box 3)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2007 Dec. (Box 3)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2008 Jan. (Box 3)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2008 Feb. (Box 3)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2008 Mar. (Box 3)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2008 Apr. (Box 3)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2008 May. (Box 3)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2008 June. (Box 3)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2008 July. (Box 3)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2008 Aug. (Box 3)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2008 Sept. (Box 3)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2008 Oct. (Box 3)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2008 Nov. (Box 3)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2008 Dec. (Box 3)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2009 Jan. (Box 3)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2009 Feb. (Box 3)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2009 Mar. (Box 3)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2009 Apr. (Box 3)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2009 May. (Box 3)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2009 June. (Box 3)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2009 July. (Box 4)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2009 Aug. (Box 4)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2009 Sept. (Box 4)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2009 Oct. (Box 4)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2009 Nov. (Box 4)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2009 Dec. (Box 4)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2010 Jan. (Box 4)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2010 Feb. (Box 4)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2010 Mar. (Box 4)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2010 Apr. (Box 4)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2010 May. (Box 4)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2010 June. (Box 4)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2010 July. (Box 4)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2010 Aug. (Box 4)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2010 Sept. (Box 4)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2010 Oct. (Box 4)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2010 Nov. (Box 4)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2010 Dec. (Box 4)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2011 Jan. (Box 4)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2011 Feb. (Box 4)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2011 Mar. (Box 4)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2011 Apr. (Box 4)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2011 May. (Box 4)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2011 June. (Box 4)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2011 July. (Box 5)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2011 Aug. (Box 5)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2011 Sept. (Box 5)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2011 Oct. (Box 5)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2011 Nov. (Box 5)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2011 Dec. (Box 5)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2012 Jan. (Box 5)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2012 Feb. (Box 5)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2012 Apr. (Box 5)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2012 May. (Box 5)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2012 June. (Box 5)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2012 July. (Box 6)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2012 Aug. (Box 6)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2012 Sept. (Box 6)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2012 Oct. (Box 6)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2012 Nov. (Box 6)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2012 Dec. (Box 6)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2013 Jan. (Box 6)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2013 Feb. (Box 6)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2013 Mar. (Box 6)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2013 Apr. (Box 6)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2013 May. (Box 6)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2013 June. (Box 6)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2013 July. (Box 6)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2013 Aug. (Box 6)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2013 Sept. (Box 6)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2013 Oct. (Box 6)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2013 Nov. (Box 6)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2013 Dec. (Box 6)
  - Tropical Storm Ernesto - SCO Daily Briefing Book, FEMA 1661 Binder, 2006. (Box 7)
  - Flood binder, 1996 Jan. (Box 7)
  - Catalog of State and Federal Mandates on Local Governments, 2006. (Box 7)
  - DHS-FEMA Individuals and Households Program ONA, 2005-2006, 2012. (Box 7)
  - Miscellaneous State Surveys on Emergency Management, undated. (Box 7)
  - VCU Performance Management Group - VEI, CMI, etc., 2009, 2011-2013. (Box 7)
  - VCU Performance Management Group - VEI, CMI, etc., 2006-2008. (Box 7)
  - VCU Permance Management Group - VEI, CMI, etc., 1998-1999, 2000-2002, 2003-2005. (Box 7)
  - Coordinator general correspondence mixed, undated. (Box 7)
  - Virginia Disaster Relief Fund Awards - Correspondence, 2013. (Box 7)
  - Virginia Disaster Assistance Donations Program, 2013. (Box 7)
  - Virginia Disaster Relief Fund Awards - Correspondence, 2011-2012. (Box 7)
  - Virginia Disaster Relief Fun - Bi-weekly reports, 2011-2012. (Box 7)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2004 Jan. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2004 Feb. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2004 Mar. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2004 Apr. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2004 May. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2004 June. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2004 July. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2004 Aug. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2004 Sept. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2004 Oct. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2004 Nov. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2004 Dec. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2005 Jan. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2005 Feb. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2005 Mar. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2005 Apr. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2005 May. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2005 June. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2005 July. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2005 Aug. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2005 Sept. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2005 Oct. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2005 Nov. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2005 Dec. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2006 Jan. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2006 Feb. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2006 Mar. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2006 Apr. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2006 May. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2006 June. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2006 July. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2006 Aug. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2006 Sept. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2006 Oct. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2006 Nov. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2006 Dec. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2007 Jan. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2007 Feb. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2007 Mar. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2007 Apr. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2007 May. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2007 June. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2007 July. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2007 Aug. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2007 Sept. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2007 Oct. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2007 Nov. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2007 Dec. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2002. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2003. (Box 8)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2008 Jan. (Box 9)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2008 Feb. (Box 9)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2008 Mar. (Box 9)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2008 Apr. (Box 9)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2008 May. (Box 9)
  - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2008 June. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2008 July. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2008 Aug. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2008 Sept. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2008 Oct. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2008 Nov. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2008 Dec. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2009 Jan. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2009 Feb. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2009 Mar. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2009 Apr. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2009 May. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2009 June. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2009 July. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2009 Aug. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2009 Sept. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2009 Oct. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2009 Nov. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2009 Dec. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2010 Jan. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2010 Feb. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2010 Mar. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2010 Apr. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2010 May. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2010 June. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2010 July. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2010 Aug. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2010 Sept. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2010 Oct. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2010 Nov. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2010 Dec. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2011 Jan. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2011 Feb. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2011 Mar. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2011 Apr. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2011 May. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2011 June. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2011 July. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2011 Aug. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2011 Sept. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2011 Oct. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2011 Nov. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2011 Dec. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2012 Jan. (Box 10)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2012 Feb. (Box 10)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2012 Mar. (Box 10)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2012 Apr. (Box 10)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2012 May. (Box 10)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2012 June. (Box 10)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2012 June. (Box 10)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2012 July. (Box 10)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2012 Aug. (Box 10)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2012 Sept. (Box 10)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2012 Oct. (Box 10)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2012 Nov. (Box 10)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2012 Dec. (Box 10)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2013 Jan. (Box 10)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2013 Feb. (Box 10)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2013 Mar. (Box 10)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2013 Apr. (Box 10)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2013 May. (Box 10)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2013 June. (Box 10)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2013 July. (Box 10)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2013 Aug. (Box 10)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2013 Sept. (Box 10)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2013 Oct. (Box 10)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2013 Nov. (Box 10)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2013 Dec. (Box 10)
  - Correspondence with Governor's Office - Chronological, 2000 Jan. (Box 11)
  - Correspondence with Governor's Office - Chronological, 2000 Feb. (Box 11)
  - Correspondence with Governor's Office - Chronological, 2000 Mar. (Box 11)
  - Correspondence with Governor's Office - Chronological, 2000 Apr. (Box 11)
  - Correspondence with Governor's Office - Chronological, 2000 May. (Box 11)
  - Correspondence with Governor's Office - Chronological, 2000 June. (Box 11)
  - Correspondence with Governor's Office - Chronological, 2000 July. (Box 11)
  - Correspondence with Governor's Office - Chronological, 2000 Aug. (Box 11)
  - Correspondence with Governor's Office - Chronological, 2000 Sept. (Box 11)
  - Correspondence with Governor's Office - Chronological, 2000 Oct. (Box 11)
  - Correspondence with Governor's Office - Chronological, 2000 Nov. (Box 11)
  - Correspondence with Governor's Office - Chronological, 2000 Dec. (Box 11)
  - Correspondence with Governor's Office - Chronological, 2001 Jan. (Box 12)
  - Correspondence with Governor's Office - Chronological, 2001 Feb. (Box 12)
  - Correspondence with Governor's Office - Chronological, 2001 Mar. (Box 12)
  - Correspondence with Governor's Office - Chronological, 2001 Apr. (Box 12)
  - Correspondence with Governor's Office - Chronological, 2001 May. (Box 12)
  - Correspondence with Governor's Office - Chronological, 2001 June. (Box 12)
  - Correspondence with Governor's Office - Chronological, 2001 July. (Box 12)
  - Correspondence with Governor's Office - Chronological, 2001 Aug. (Box 12)
  - Correspondence with Governor's Office - Chronological, 2001 Sept. (Box 12)
  - Correspondence with Governor's Office - Chronological, 2001 Oct. (Box 12)
  - Correspondence with Governor's Office - Chronological, 2001 Nov. (Box 12)
  - Correspondence with Governor's Office - Chronological, 2001 Dec. (Box 12)
  - Correspondence with Governor's Office - Chronological, 2002 Jan. (Box 13)
  - Correspondence with Governor's Office - Chronological, 2002 Feb. (Box 13)
  - Correspondence with Governor's Office - Chronological, 2002 Mar. (Box 13)
  - Correspondence with Governor's Office - Chronological, 2002 Apr. (Box 13)
  - Correspondence with Governor's Office - Chronological, 2002 May. (Box 13)
  - Correspondence with Governor's Office - Chronological, 2002 June. (Box 13)
  - Correspondence with Governor's Office - Chronological, 2002 July. (Box 13)
  - Correspondence with Governor's Office - Chronological, 2002 Aug. (Box 13)
  - Correspondence with Governor's Office - Chronological, 2002 Sept. (Box 13)
  - Correspondence with Governor's Office - Chronological, 2002 Oct. (Box 13)
  - Correspondence with Governor's Office - Chronological, 2002 Nov. (Box 13)
  - Correspondence with Governor's Office - Chronological, 2002 Dec. (Box 13)
  - Weekly reports to the Secretary, 2003 Dec-2011 Dec. (Box 14)
  - Correspondence with Secretary, 2003-2013. (Box 15)
  - Governor's correspondence, 2011. (Box 16)
  - Governor's correspondence, 2012. (Box 16)
  - Governor's correspondence, 2013. (Box 16)
  - Governor's Award nominations, 2011. (Box 16)
  - Chief of Staff correspondence, 2011. (Box 16)
  - Governor's event forms, 2010-2011. (Box 16)
  - Governor's Decision Briefs, 2010-2011. (Box 16)
  - General correspondence - Governor McDonnell, 2010. (Box 16)
  - General correspondence - Governor's Chief of Staff, 2010. (Box 16)
  - Disaster Reports / Governor's Declaration (McDonnell Administration), 2010-2013. (Box 16)
  - Governor's Office correspondence, 2009. (Box 16)
  - Governor's Office correspondence, 2008. (Box 16)
  - Governor's Office correspondence, 2007. (Box 16)
  - Governor's Office correspondence, 2006. (Box 16)
  - Governor's Office correspondence, 2004-2005. (Box 16)
  - Governor's Office correspondence, 2002-2003. (Box 16)
  - Book chapter for Governor, undated. (Box 16)
  - Lt. Governor's Office, 2000. (Box 16)
  - Decision briefs for Governor, 1998-2002. (Box 16)
  - Transition Team, undated. (Box 16)
  - Briefing for Governor-Elect Gilmore, 1997 Dec 12. (Box 16)
  - Governor Gilmore - General correspondence, 1998-2001. (Box 16)
  - Chief of Staff - General correspondence, 1998-2001. (Box 16)
  - Governor's Budget Decision Package, 1998-1999. (Box 16)
  - Governor's Budget Decision Package, 1996. (Box 16)
  - Governor's Budget Decision Package, 1995 Nov. (Box 16)
  - Governor's Budget Decision Package, 1995 Sept-Oct. (Box 16)
  - Approval Forms - Governor Gilmore, 1998-2001. (Box 16)
  - Approval Forms - Procurement Over $25,000 (Gilmore Administration), 1998-2001. (Box 16)
  - Secretary of Administration, 1998-2001. (Box 16)
  - Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1998-2013. (Box 16)
  - Secretary of Commerce and Trade, 2002. (Box 16)
  - Secretary of Education, 2008. (Box 16)
  - Secretary of Technology, 1998-2008. (Box 16)
  - Secretary of Veterns Affairs and Homeland Security, 2003. (Box 16)
  - Secretary of Veterns Affairs and Homeland Security, 2004. (Box 16)
  - Secretary of Veterns Affairs and Homeland Security, 2005. (Box 16)
  - Secretary of Veterns Affairs and Homeland Security, 2006. (Box 16)
  - Secretary of Veterns Affairs and Homeland Security, 2007. (Box 16)
  - Secretary of Veterns Affairs and Homeland Security, 2008. (Box 16)
  - Secretary of Veterns Affairs and Homeland Security, 2009. (Box 16)
  - Secretary of Veterns Affairs and Homeland Security, 2010. (Box 16)
  - Secretary of Veterns Affairs and Homeland Security, 2011. (Box 16)
  - Secretary of Veterns Affairs and Homeland Security, 2012. (Box 16)
  - Secretary of Veterns Affairs and Homeland Security, 2013. (Box 16)
  - Secure Virginia Panel Chairman John Hager, 2002-2003. (Box 16)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources, 2002. (Box 16)
  - Transition presentation, 2012-2013. (Box 17)
  - Transition presentation, 2002-2103. (Box 17)
  - Transition presentation, 2008-2009. (Box 17)
  - Secretary of Public Safety forms (McDonnell Administration), 2010-2013. (Box 17)
  - Secretary of Public Safety form (Kaine Administration), 2006-2010. (Box 17)
  - Approval forms for Secretary's Office, undated. (Box 17)